hello YouTube channel this is day 7 of
my hundred day challenge I punched it in
to the calculator yesterday online and I
wanted to see what 19 weeks from now is
and it's January 1st so how perfect that
I'm gonna be starting a new year after
these videos and what a different life I
may or may not be leaving then I have
open to it all and today I wanted to
talk about this idea well my idea the
idea that our world is designed for a
very specific group of people to succeed
CEO types extroverts type-a
personalities people that are naturally
morning people naturally people people
and it's gotten us to where we are but
we need everyone and to if we need
everyone we need to have a system that
allows everyone to flourish and be their
best self their true self whatever that
is and I can guarantee you not
everyone's morning person not everyone's
an extrovert not everyone is a Type A
personality we don't want them or need
them to be we need them to be themselves
so we need to be able to set up systems
that allow people who are more shy who
are more introverted who are more you
know want to have part of the work on
their own or in groups or we need to
able to meet people where they are and
I'll help them to be they're not even
necessarily pulled about a bit unless
they're Nazis and then once called on
back that's not that's not healthy for
anyone but figuring out a way to let
everyone I was watching a little bit of
a crush I'm part of this Facebook group
called AOL evolve you know allowed Kyle
cease and there's people who post crush
on a few people there's been a few
people add pressure on and I'd like to
stock the Facebook page and see if maybe
they are gay or not and this person is
clearly gay because they said that they
were gay and said that they had a hard
coming out story and so then I was um a
little bit stalking her
well her YouTube channel I don't know if
that's called stalking
and she's amazing but she was talking
about how you find your purpose and I
was like half an hour I don't know if I
watched it all amazing about and talking
about need to take action and that's
what I'm finding problems with is I do
stay way too much in my head and I need
to be more in my heart I mean my head is
what convinced me I didn't like women
for so many years
who wasn't listening to my heart and I
don't know this whole journey I've been
on the last few years of self-discovery
which I thought I mean I've been doing
it for 20 years but I kind of took off
the rules where I know you think there
is a place to get to I'm successful
right now I'm a single mom on disability
and I realize I'm not society's idea of
successful but I'm happy and at peace
for the first time in my life I'm just
okay exactly where I am I'm so grateful
for a system that allows me to not work
full time to realize that that's exactly
what I needed I'm grateful for my
daughter being in daycare and having
that space where she's able to go and
interact with people that I wouldn't be
able to I can't take her to the park
every day and I've been able to go on
this journey of discovering what I need
to be healthy and what I need to be well
as healthy as I possibly can be I'm
still in pain I'm still tired all the
time and I am I love it because it has
given me access to this time and space
to come up with these ideas but also
it's exactly what I've needed to be and
what I need to go through to be who I
need to be on this planet from the
purpose I was put here for because I do
know what purpose I was put here for and
it's two things one of which is probably
not so important to everyone else which
is to be a mother it's my daughter
I felt her calling from the other side
which is why I chose to become a single
parent and have a child and clearly I
was so supposed to have her she is just
like the perfect child for me
and hopefully I'm the perfect mother for
her and the other thing is this project
is global cooperative it's gonna allow
us all to live abundant amazing lives
that are designed to be happy and give
our purpose and contribute in a way that
only we can contribute that only like
you as an individual can contribute in
and I'm not a type-a personality I'm not
a CEO type I'm not someone who can just
like go get it all done by myself in
fact even if I wanted to be my health
limitations make it nearly impossible
and how beautiful is that that I need
other people to create something that
needs other people and yeah that I just
want to create yourself like on the
verge of time and I love that if I had
it happen as a child like I love it for
my kid maybe I would have figured out
how to deal with those emotions and not
have them constantly bubbling up but I
didn't and who knows if I ever will but
I love it I love feeling the full range
of emotions and not pushing them down
and allowing myself to be me and now I
just have to free everybody else and as
I raise myself over to poverty I'm
bringing everybody with me and this is
where I what I know how to do at the
moment and I was watching YouTube videos
and realizing how much well they're much
better at them than I am she's sorry
she's much better at them than I am and
I do need to definitely get better and
that's something I'll be doing over the
course of these hundred days too is
hopefully figuring out how to edit how
to sit and talk for an hour I mean I
think she pauses them daily or she was
posting them daily at any rate and she's
still managed to edit them and have
little I mean clearly she's better at
this than I am
but I'm figuring out how to edit videos
and how to do better because I clearly
I'm not so succinct when I talk and so
when I'm not editing videos five minutes
is
I can't even really get into too much so
later I'm gonna do a video that is me
talking for two hours if I need to talk
for two hours and then I'm gonna edit it
down into I just feels like then I need
to have makeup on then I need to have my
hair done then I need to do all that
stuff who's gonna be like an official
video and I don't want that I don't want
that to feel that strain on me I'm gonna
go hang out with my friend today which
is why I am getting why I'm doing this
now and why my hair is wet and all that
good stuff and I will be back tomorrow
day seven
we all need a system that allows us to
be who we are and contribute what we
want to contribute